[ Episode 1 ]
[ I have a favorite movie scene. ]
[ It's the opening scene of ]
[ Audrey Hepburn's movie,
"Breakfast at Tiffany's". ]
[ Audrey gets off a taxi ]
[ and walks as if she rules the world. ]
[ And she stares into a jewelry shop. ]
[ Jewelry, Perusahaan Desain Perhiasan ]
[ She has a bite of the bread ]
[ and drinks a sip of the coffee. ]
[ I like this scene ]
[ because she's eating alone. ]
[ As she marvels at the beautiful jewelry, ]
[ she's enjoying her bread
without anyone's interruption. ]
[ It's the moment when one's view, ]
[ tastebud, and mental state
form the best combination. ]
Do-hee.
Yeong-dong.
Give it to me. Let me cut it for you.
You must sprinkle a lot of black pepper.
It gets rid of the gamey odor.
[ Your significant other gets in the way. ]
- It looks hot.
- Is that so?
[ But the time you spend
with your loved ones is important too. ]
- Where should we go?
Let's go.
[ Sometimes, you're willing
to give up on everything ]
[ as long as you can have dinner
while feeling the warmth from him. ]
[ At times in life, ]
[ the combination of ideal factors
isn't what's important. ]
[ It's the only thing that makes you
bear through everything. ]
My goodness!
Come on.
Move!
I told you not to chase me.
If you keep chasing me,
I'll kill everyone!
Is that Chinese?
Calm down.
No need to get worked up. Calm down.
- Bring my girlfriend now.
- Wait.
What's he saying?
What does he want me to bring?
Why did I stop going to Chinese classes?
I'm sorry. Could you repeat that?
I'm not very good at Chinese.
Bring my woman to me.
Your woman? Your girlfriend?
I got it. I understood you. Okay.
I promise I'll bring her here.
Please calm down.
You're going to die soon.
No. I don't want to die.
No, I don't want that.
I'm sorry. Sorry!
I meant to say
that you're going to get better.
Don't worry. You're not going to die.
Calm down. Put it down.
Put down the knife.
Shut your mouth!
You're okay.
Don't worry. You're okay.
- Okay. Thanks.
- That was so cool.
Where did he go?
Wait. Hold on. Move, please.
Hey, where have you been all this time?
You got him.
- Is he okay?
- Hey, call an ambulance.
An ambulance?
[ Gol-lum ]
[ Of course,
the rent is ridiculously high. ]
But the company is going to cover half.
How can I commute from home?
The round trip takes four hours.
I'll die on the street.
How's Dad?
[ - He's acting up again. ]
- What is it?
[ He's been dressing up a lot lately
and going out. ]
[ Here's my guess. I bet he's seeing
the owner of the new cafe. ]
This isn't his first time.
Whether you fight
or settle, you guys should handle this.
[ If your boyfriend, Yeong-dong,
cheats on you, ]
[ you have to cut his thing off
right away. ]
[ Just like how we cut
the tip of pickled radish. ]
Mom, please stop.
I won't live with a husband
who tortures me
by having affairs with other women.
Don't worry about me.
- That will never happen.
[ - My gosh. ]
[ Men are all the same. ]
[ - Didn't I... ]
- Stop it.
Is that such a nice thing
to say to your daughter?
Don't skip your meals. Bye.
[ Hey, Do-hee. ]
My gosh. These Woos!
Goodness.
But why isn't he calling me today?
I'm moving today.
- Good day.
What a relief. The patient seems fine.
He's lucky that we got him.
Or things would've been bad for him.
- I'm beat.
- Oh, right.
- What took you so long to get here?
- What do you mean?
You took the motorcycle,
and I had to run here.
I see. You walked here.
Dr. Kim. Did you eat?
- Eat by yourself.
- You want sushi and soba?
That sounds good.
[ Monday, May 4, 2020 ]
[ I'm working right now.
Please leave a message. ]
Is he busy?
[ You must be busy. ]
[ Happy birthday! ]
[ This is your third birthday
we're spending together. ]
[ I'm sorry that we never got to
celebrate your birthday together. ]
[ But someday, we'll be together
on your birthdays, right? ]
Right!
[ Recipes for boyfriends ]
[ 2N Box ]
Let me try pork belly and tripe.
It's hot!
- Are you okay?
- What are you doing?
Hey, change it. Darn it.
This...
I'm done.
Today, I cleaned the ear to cheer up
your exhausted souls.
I'll pluck out the nose hair next week.
Until we meet again,
take care.
Okay. Good work.
My goodness. I'm starving.
Let's eat.
Great. Nice.
More, more. More. Come on.
Yes. That's it.
Come on.
Nice.
I heard you moved to Seoul.
But you came to work late.
Do you also check
what time I come to work?
Well, you know. I'm never late.
You're never late because
you practically live in the office.
You should change your clothes.
Our office smells like the wet mop
from school after a rainy season.
It's nice. It brings back memories.
Okay?
Are you going somewhere?
Well, yes.
How could you take days off
when we're crazy busy these days?
You must be confident
you won't make mistakes today.
I have never messed up
when the show is live.
My lame and silly approach
is my show's identity.
And that's why my viewers watch my show.
You sure have a grand idea
when it's only a third-rate show.
It's not a third-rate show!
My show is supposed to be silly.
I'll be watching your show today.
You have three seconds.
Ready.
- Action.
- Hello. It's "Do Whatever You Want".
I'm your host, Jjoda Man.
Gosh, today's show will be amazing.
We have invited one of the viewers
who got royally dumped
by her boyfriend who cheated on her.
As we talk behind his back,
we're going to drink in broad daylight.
- Nice to meet you.
[ - This is so lame. ]
This is Ma-ya.
She's not the singer.
Hello, I'm Ma-ya.
Before I sober up, make me a drink.
[ - This doesn't look fun. ]
- I'll make it quick.
Mix, mix, and mix. I'll make one for you.
- All right. Cheers.
- Cheers.
[ This is over the line. ]
[ Cheers. ]
You made a good one.
- This is nice.
- Right? It hits the spot.
Where was I? Right.
He...
That jerk...
[ My gosh, I can't watch this anymore. ]
That dog
would go crazy whenever he sees women.
How could he look at other women
when he has me? I'm pretty, you know.
From what you told me, it sounds like
you'd been on his back
a lot.
Wait.
- Okay. Great.
- Let's say that I had been.
Then, does it mean he can cheat on me?
Perhaps, he wasn't having an affair.
He could have found his true love.
- Hey. Are you serious?
- Have you gone mad?
My gosh, I can't believe you.
You look like you have a nasty temper.
That's right. I have a nasty temper.
Let me show you
how nasty my temper can get today.
- You.
- Wait.
- My goodness.
- I'll pluck all of your hair.
Hey, it's my hair.
- I'll pluck every single strand.
- I'll do the same.
- What? Hey.
- My goodness. Hey.
- You started first.
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
- My hair.
- Score. This is it!
- Goodness.
- I'm losing hair, man.
- I'm sorry.
- Nice!
- What are you doing?
- Hey. The number of views...
- Stay out of this.
- Do you want to lose hair too?
- Hey.
- But still.
- Give me two more minutes.
- Look at the view count.
- Hey!
What are you staring at?
Is this funny? Is this funny to you?
Okay, fine.
You should also get a taste of this.
Get a taste of this!
This is good.
[ CEO Nam Ah-yeong ]
[iQIYI Ver] MBC E01 'Dinner Mate'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Darn it.
"I didn't do anything wrong.
Why is she mad at me?"
You must be thinking that.
My show got over 100,000 hits.
What's the problem?
But your show was such a mess!
My goodness. You've really changed
compared to when you started.
You were the one who named
our company's name 2N Box.
You named it after two Ns
from "not normal".
We're not normal.
So I did something that's not normal.
Hey, Do-hee.
We're past the point
when we worked with two monitors
in a small studio in Ssangmun-dong.
That's why other producers are making
good-quality shows as you requested.
At least, I ought to do this. Shouldn't I?
Anyway, as of today, you can't do
these inappropriate items.
Or we'll be blocked.
"Blocked"? As if.
Where are your manners? I'm your boss.
Yes, ma'am.
I will show you my manners.
I can't agree to that.
Do whatever you want.
And I'm using my vacation days.
So fire me now if you want to.
You're going to leave
after making a huge mess?
Once I arrive in Jeju Island,
I'll send you Jeju oranges.
Do-hee! Hey!
Hey. You...
[ Yes. ]
I'm sorry.
The doctor really hates being on TV.
Okay. If he changes his mind,
I'll call you right back.
Okay.
Dr. Kim.
Everyone is dying to hire you for
their shows. Why won't you even try?
You know that it's not my style.
What is it? Did another show call?
Why on earth not?
You've got the looks.
And you're more than qualified.
And you are eloquent beyond this world.
Why won't you star on TV shows?
So that you can die in frustration.
Didn't you know?
And most importantly, I don't want to.
I don't care about that.
Let me be blunt. Did your family
take out a private loan?
Or do you have a lot of ex-girlfriends
who want to kill you?
Hey.
Yes?
You're a mind reader.
You sure are.
I'll take care of that. Don't worry.
Pick me up at the airport this evening.
Don't be late.
Since you're going down there,
take a day off.
Go to a cafe by Woljeong Beach
and have a cup of caramel macchiato.
If you spot a single woman,
why don't you...
[ Kim Hae-kyong ]
- Give her a card, you know.
- No.
If you don't want to be on TV,
you should at least date someone.
This research paper says single people
die earlier than people who are obese.
Did you know that or not?
Really?
Yes.
I'll start binge-eating as of today
to outlive those single people.
I'm off now.
He won't even let me have anything.
He's annoyingly logical.
Darn it.
You're really not going to call him first?
Of course not. It will be a surprise.
My gosh, it's making me nervous.
From the vibe I get from him,
it looks like he's going to propose.
What? Really? No way.
Are you feeling it this time?
[ Yeong-dong ]
[ Out of the blue, he sent me
a photo of a ring last week. ]
He'll propose for sure.
So I asked what it was for.
He told me his friend asked if the ring
looked okay for a proposal.
But he had no clue if it was good,
so he wanted to know what I thought.
That's cute.
Hey, so are you going to run a cafe
in Jeju Island as a couple
and live like Lee Hyo-ri?
I guess so.
I'll be back with my ring right here.
- Right here.
- Here.
- See you.
- Okay, see you soon.
What a lucky brat.
Hey, Yeong-dong.
It is currently May 4, 1:30 p.m.
Three hours before landing in Jeju Island.
You have no idea I'm on my way right now.
I'm recording this because I have a hunch
we're going to have
a historic moment together.
I'm going to show this
to our future kids too.
I'm blushing.
Enjoy your trip.
Here.
I'm checking in now.
I hope I get a front seat
so I can stretch my legs.
Ms. Woo Do-hee, we've upgraded your seat
to business class.
- Enjoy your trip.
- No way.
Thank you.
I've got a good feeling about this.
I feel like the world is helping me
and blessing us.
I'm feeling good even before departing.
Right, Yeong-dong?
I'm boarding business class. Let's go.
No way.
This is so cool! I love it.
It's a whole new world.
Here's my seat.
My feet don't touch the ground.
I feel like I'm on a trampoline.
This is awesome.
Excuse me. Would you like anything
to drink before we take off?
- I'd like water. Lukewarm water.
- Yes, sir.
I'd like sikhye.
I'm sorry, but we don't have sikhye.
Right?
Then I'd like one cold Coke, please.
I'll get one icy Coke for you.
[ Medical Chart ]
[ Medical Chart,
Patient Name: Park Geun-hee ]
It's practically a bed.
What's this?
This is mindblowing.
- Excuse me, Ms. Flight Attendant.
- Yes, ma'am?
- I have a favor to ask.
- Sure, what is it?
I think I might get a proposal today.
Oh, really? Congratulations.
So I'm recording congratulatory messages
on this camera.
Would you mind doing one for me?
Of course, ma'am.
Okay, I'm ready.
- Cue.
- Ms. Bride-to-be...
My apologies. I'll do it again.
Cue.
Congratulations to
the groom-to-be's proposal
and your upcoming wedding.
Don't forget to travel with our airline
for your honeymoon.
- Wishing all the best for you two.
- Cut.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure, I envy you.
- If you need any help, please let me know.
- Okay.
Excuse me, can I get more water, please?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Sir.
- I'd like to ask a favor.
- I can't do it.
Okay.
- But still...
- I won't do it.
Okay.
What a snobby fellow.
- He's got zero generosity.
- Excuse me?
What is up with this guy?
Is he a psychic or what?
[ Are you serious? ]
Yes, with the coupon event,
you get a free upgrade
to a new sedan model.
Oh, my gosh.
Can't you see, Yeong-dong?
The world is showering me with luck
as if I was destined to receive it.
This Jeju trip is a bundle
of blessings over blessings.
Awesome possum. This is amazing, blazing.
[ Medical Chart ]
[ Medical Notes ]
[ Lee Byeong-jin ]
[ Would you like to have dinner together
when you come back to Seoul? ]
[ No, thanks. Help yourself. ]
[ Lee Byeong-jin ]
- Hey.
[ - Dr. Kim. ]
You skip your meals most of the time
when you
[ do diet counseling, and I'm only trying
to take care of you. ]
Why can't you just say yes
and agree to eat with me...
I like eating alone. Okay?
Bye.
Yeong-dong.
I'm going to present one extravagant
birthday meal for you, okay?
[ Pork ]
[ Silky Seaweed ]
Should I cook him suyuk?
I'm getting both.
Champagne.
We can't miss drinks
on such a historic day.
I'm getting a strong one.
I'm sorry for having you come over
such a long way.
No, it's fine. I love Jeju Island.
Yes.
Well, why don't we eat first?
- Please pick what you'd like.
- Okay.
What should I get?
- It's my first time to eat at this place.
- I see.
May I take a look? This place is unique
because they use capellini pasta.
It's very thin and light.
It goes great with pasta salads.
The signature menu here is
the salmon pasta salad.
Would you like to try that?
Sure.
[ The omega-3 fatty acids in salmon ]
[ stimulate the brain cells. ]
Okay.
[ It also increases dopamine
and serotonin, neurotransmitters ]
[ - that control our moods. ]
- Over here.
I feel like it's all my fault.
[ First, one's words
and actions slow down. ]
[ It means one's thoughts
and judgments are blurred. ]
I was weak.
Maybe
I'm being punished.
[ Second, one may put the blame
on themselves. ]
[ One may believe all misfortunes happened
because of them. ]
[ Third, one may gather all the plates
in front of them. ]
[ They can't afford to care for others. ]
Other people
seem to move on after breakups.
I feel like I'm falling into a deeper pit
as days go by.
It's really
hard to move on.
[ Fourth, one stops eating. ]
Okay. I'm going in now.
See you soon.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
- Sung-doo.
- Hi, Producer Woo!
- How's it going?
- I'm good.
Go in, Yeong-dong's inside.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Yeong-dong is upstairs, right?
- He's out at the moment.
Did you call him before coming?
No. I'm here to surprise him.
Oh, I see.
I'll wait upstairs.
Oh, we're sterilizing that floor
so you can't go now.
Producer Woo...
[ Stop it. ]
[ Stop what? ]
[ Stop it, it's tickly. ]
[ Are you sure? ]
Do... Do-hee.
Wait, it's her.
What?
You're proposing
to that passenger?
Oh, I see you've met in advance
on the plane.
You said you ended things with her.
I did...
Speak up, will you?
You got a new action camera.
I know a friend who runs
a sole agency for these.
Excuse me?
You've changed your hairstyle.
It looks good on you.
It's been the same for two years.
Is that so?
Then, did your face change?
Oh, maybe not that.
You son of...
I feel like I'm the only one
trapped in this state.
No, I feel like I'm falling into
a deeper pit.
Everyone else seems to move on
after a breakup
as if it was a slight cold.
How about this?
Think of it as a cold
that's lasting a bit longer.
[ You! ]
Please enjoy your meals, customers.
You guys are dead.
Enjoy your meal.
I was going to take my time
and explain it all.
[ "Take my time"? ]
[ Are you evangelizing someone to church? ]
[ How on earth were you going to explain ]
[ that you're dumping me
because of a new girl? ]
Hey.
Hey, don't hit me. Violence is bad.
[ Hey, let's calm down. ]
Goodness.
Get up.
[ I think I might ]
get a proposal today.
So I'm recording congratulatory messages
on this camera.
Hurry and get in here!
Okay, I'll get up.
Quit your slapstick comedy acts
- and make sure you end things right.
- Okay.
You, shut it.
Don't hit me.
Aren't you going to continue
with the recording?
It is a very crucial moment right now.
Cue.
Ms. Bride-to-be...
Excuse me?
I can still give you
my congratulatory message.
Please stop.
- Why that crazy wench!
- Wait! Stop!
I mean,
you shouldn't scar
a flight attendant's face.
Are you saying it's not okay
to scar her face,
but it's okay to scar my pride?
No, that's...
Look here, Miss.
I hate this situation as much as you do.
Why don't you leave after venting
by yanking my hair out,
or send in a certified file that contains
all of your curses?
Make up your mind.
Don't forget to enjoy your sikhye
and take a breather.
What a new-school lunatic.
- Get over here, you wench!
- Hey, don't do this.
Come to your senses and let's talk it out.
Let's talk things out in a calm manner.
I should hang you
once I come to my senses!
[ Episode 2 ]
Fine.
Give me an objective reason
that's at least convincing.
Wait.
[ A reaction caused by
an external stimulus. ]
[ A positive sign. ]
[ A convincing reason? ]
Yes.
Well, it's not a very flashy reason.
At least let me hear it.
I don't know when it began,
but I started to hate picking up
your calls 80 percent of the time.
I started to think of excuses
instead of finding where to go
when you wanted to go on a trip.
I stopped saving your photos
whenever you sent them to me.
When I listened to love songs,
I started to only think
of the singer who sang it.
Why that crude punk.
What a brazen rascal.
I want to hit him right on his syrinx
real hard.
- Right. He's so brazen.
- What a piece of garbage.
Sorry, but can everyone please quiet down?
What a detailed reasoning.
- Is that it?
- No.
This is the main reason.
I started to hate eating with you.
- Gosh.
- What is she going to do?
- How could he say that?
- Poor her.
- What is up with him?
- Exactly. Oh, no.
You should be willing to eat
with someone you love, right?
But
with you, it became a duty.
I didn't eat because I wanted to,
but because I had to.
If you were going to end things like this,
why did you send me a ring photo?
That was...
Hey, what should I do?
- What should I do?
- Why?
What's wrong, sir?
I accidentally sent the ring photo
to Do-hee.
- Gosh.
- You should always double-check
the photos when you're two-timing.
I checked the photos,
but I accidentally sent it to her.
- How should I...
- Goodness.
What should I do?
Just tell her that your friend is using it
for his proposal.
Tell her you just wanted
to ask an opinion about it.
- Good one.
- Oh, right.
That photo?
I sent it by accident.
I'm really sorry.
I will accept any punishment.
My mom told me
I should just cut your thing off
if you ever cheat on me.
Just like how we cut
the tip of pickled radish.
That's a bit...
The tip of pickled radish
can be ground and put in dumplings
and seasonings though. But yours
is useless.
Just take good care of it.
- Goodness.
- No way.
- Thank you, Do-hee.
- It's been awful,
and let's never see each other again.
You scumbag.
I will take the champagne.
I have a happy occasion to celebrate.
since I got rid of trash like you.
You have it.
Do-hee...
Do-hee.
Hey.
- Let go.
- If you leave like this...
Do you want me to break it with
your forehead to see what's inside?
[ Dyspnoea. ]
[ Tachycardia. ]
[ Panic attack caused by excitement. ]
- Wait.
- Don't follow her.
But still...
If you want to follow her,
break up with me first.
I'm sorry. Let's go.
Eun-seo.
This is great.
This is just amazing.
Why are you doing this again?
This is pathetic.
Doctor.
Doctor?
Yes?
I'm sorry. Let's start over.
Do you think she will be okay?
She will need some time,
but eventually, she will be fine.
How can you be sure?
- Excuse me?
- Only those who have been hurt
can understand those who are hurt.
She's betrayed. She can't be fine.
[ Why do you ]
look like you haven't lost anything?
I'm sure she needs someone like you.
Well...
I'm not sure.
I'm not good at relationships myself.
- I don't know...
- Doctor.
Please help her.
If she recovers,
I will feel like I can be saved as well.
Everyone!
The doctor sitting here
is a famous psychiatrist.
- Wait...
- This doctor
will help the woman over there.
Wait. What are you doing?
Doctor.
- Wait...
- Doctor.
Doctor.
I will cheer for you, Doctor.
- Please help her.
- Doctor.
He's going to help her!
Good luck!
You're awesome, Doctor!
- Taxi!
- You got this!
Please follow the white car in the front.
- Over there.
- Okay.
Okay, bye!
What a dynamic day.
Maybe I should buy a lottery.
I'm sure I can win the first prize.
What is it that you did so wrong?
Tell me about it.
Excuse me? I'm not the one...
I have been driving a cab
in Jeju Island for 27 years now.
I have seen over 70,000 men and women
who drove home with rental cars
after having fights.
- That's not it.
- I understand.
So what did you do?
Did you have different opinions
on the itinerary?
Or did she make you tell her
about your memories here
with your ex-girlfriend
with leading questions?
I got it.
"Don't you know why I'm angry?"
- Is this what happened?
- Can you just focus on following her?
That's not it.
Sure, sure. I got it.
Could you please stop the car here?
- Thank you.
This place is
a popular photo spot these days.
Make up with her and deep kiss her.
- Okay.
- You can do it!
- Okay, okay.
- Good.
Thank you!
Gosh, he's cute.
I wonder if the girl is pretty too.
Darn it. I came here to
get some fresh air.
But only the salty air is
coming through my nose.
My goodness. What's happening?
What on earth is she doing?
I might actually end up falling.
Excuse me!
Hey!
What are you doing?
What's his problem?
Oh, no!
Goodness.
Hey.
Wake up!
Wait. What?
Are you okay?
Who are you?
Why did you suddenly run to me?
I didn't know you would dodge like that.
Of course I dodged.
I can't just let some man tackle me.
You were trying to kill yourself, right?
Why would I kill myself?
Af the cafe earlier,
I saw you being humiliated.
You were there?
Yes.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
You seem to like
meddling with others' business.
What? What kind of attitude is that?
I was only trying to help you
with good intentions.
I'm the one who saved
a drowning person's life.
Gosh.
I knew it. I knew she wouldn't die.
Don't you have to go and see a doctor?
You seem to have hurt your head.
I'm fine.
So just go with your friend
standing next to you.
"Friend"?
Who is standing next to me?
The person next to you who looks like you.
What do you mean by the person next to me?
What on earth?
Are you a psychic?
The person next to you
who is dressed like you.
Isn't she your friend?
Hey, there's blood
on the back of your head.
What?
[iQIYI Ver] MBC E02 'Dinner Mate'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Oh, no! Oh, my gosh!
[ Jeju Haseong Hospital ]
External force was applied
to the occipital region,
which led to unconsciousness.
Unconsciousness can be caused
by an interruption in blood circulation,
functional impairment of neurons,
central nervous system disorders,
and damaged reticular formation.
But it's hard to give an exact diagnosis.
How bad is it?
An injury can be followed
by low body temperature,
pale face, tachycardia, and acrotism.
So what's your diagnosis, Doctor?
Cerebral concussion.
So what's that cerebral thing?
It's a concussion of the brain.
Cerebral means brain.
A concussion of the brain, I see.
A concussion of the brain?
You mean, the injury you get when you hit
your head and get dizzy?
Yes. That's it.
The test result was all right.
It's only a minor laceration.
The sutured wound was only this big.
He will be moved to a general ward,
and he can go home as soon as he wakes up.
Why does he make it sound
all so difficult?
[ He didn't get on the airplane? ]
Did he take a boat then?
Oh, it was an airport. I'm sorry.
Okay.
What's going on?
He wouldn't answer my phone
nor has he taken the flight.
What time is it again?
Oh, it's 7:57 p.m.
If only I didn't meddle
with others' business,
I'd have already landed at Gimpo Airport,
be driving
on the south of Dongjak Bridge by now.
So you live near Gangnam.
Right?
I should cancel all my evening schedules.
Darn it.
What?
Maybe I should wash my hair.
The nurse said
you shouldn't wash your hair
and keep the wound from water.
Push this part and...
- Where are my clothes?
- They're here.
In there.
You should've taken them out to dry...
As a token of my apology,
I got you some clothes to wear.
Here.
Here you go.
Okay. I'll take that ticket.
Thank you. Okay.
I'm glad you can still buy a ticket.
Are you enjoying this?
You're enjoying this now, aren't you?
You think this is funny?
- Well...
- Answer me.
Were these extremely vintage clothes
really all you could find?
I'm sorry.
There was only one clothing store
in front of the hospital.
Goodness.
How am I supposed to
go to the airport like this?
I don't have time to buy new clothes.
Are you sure
you didn't mean to mess with me?
No way.
This is unbelievable.
Hey.
I just really need to tell you this.
You look like Kim Soo-mi
on "Granny's Got Talent".
Are you laughing now?
Are you laughing
after making me look like this?
Fine. Laugh. Keep laughing.
They say laughing will bring you luck.
Keep laughing.
I'll get going. Let's end
our weird relationship here.
Let me drive you to the airport.
I'm good. I'll take a taxi.
No.
What now? What will you do now?
What is it?
- What is it?
- I mean...
I'm on my way to the airport anyway.
You wouldn't let me pay
for the hospital bill
and the flight ticket.
Please let me do it
as a token of my apology.
Please.
[ Then you should have called me earlier. ]
[ I thought something bad
happened to you. ]
Why? Did you wish so?
Doctor, how did you
see me through?
You punk.
I'll see you when I get there.
By the way, whose phone is this?
What?
Just someone I know.
Anyway, pick me up at the airport.
[ Okay. Have a safe trip back. ]
- Okay.
[ - Be careful not to overspeed. ]
- Why don't you slow down?
[ - The speed limit is 80km per hour. ]
There are no speed cameras at this time.
[ I know this road well. ]
Hello?
Is that a woman?
[ Relax Psychiatric Clinic ]
Gosh. When I told him to go on a date,
he said he wasn't interested,
trying to look cool and everything.
What a liar.
Wait, wait!
Watch where you're going!
Oh, come on!
Is the brake just for decoration?
What's wrong with you?
You're such a cowardly man.
What a day.
I'm not sure
if you're feeling better or worse now.
What do you mean?
Oh, because I was dumped by a man?
Gosh, now I remember it.
I don't have any regrets.
I can find another man
when I get back to Seoul.
There are tons of men
waiting for me out there.
Sure.
Good for you. I'm so jealous.
I wanted to send you off at the entrance.
I'm good. It's right there.
I'm very sorry for what happened today.
Aren't you coming?
I'm flying out tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Then why...
I was worried about you.
What?
Why does he make it sound
all so difficult?
[ When I was at the hospital,
the doctor said... ]
Still, you should keep an eye on him.
He may look fine,
but if he suddenly collapses,
he can be brain-dead.
I would like to stay for one more day
to think more.
I can see the lights from the airplanes
and stars here.
They actually look quite nice.
Then have a safe trip back to Seoul.
Did I hear it right?
You should eat something first.
Bye, then.
When something bad happens,
most people think
they are the only unhappy ones.
If that's what you're thinking,
please don't.
Happiness has eyes,
but unhappiness doesn't.
It just chooses
anyone randomly.
It's so pretty.
Your boyfriend seems to have spent
quite a lot of money.
I didn't expect to hear such big news
only after a quarter of the day.
- Did he officially propose to you?
- Yes.
Some obstacle butted in
and spoiled the mood though.
"Obstacle"?
- What's that?
- It's a long story.
[ Obstacle? ]
Where should I go?
[ Mandarin chocolate ]
What is it?
Mandarin chocolate.
Buy some mandarin chocolate.
I'm good, thanks.
Darn it.
[ This is the main reason. ]
I started to hate eating with you.
That scumbag.
I pretended that I liked
the steak covered with pepper
for him.
[ This is an announcement
for passengers on Flight 908. ]
[ The boarding gate has been changed ]
[ from Gate 47 to Gate 43. ]
[ Now I think about it again, ]
I'm really sorry for what has happened.
Today is one of the days
when the whole universe
is bullying me as if
it's planned beforehand.
On days like this,
every one of my blood vessel
in the heart hurts.
It feels like my blood vessel is
filled with capsaicin.
I wonder why misfortune always finds me
every once in a while.
[ You may say it's too much to mention ]
[ big words like universe and heart ]
over just a guy.
No matter how much I loved him
and how long I have dated him,
breaking up is heartbreaking.
Being left alone
hurts a lot.
[ "Being left alone". ]
[ It's really strange. ]
I'm the one leaving you,
but why do I feel like
I'm being left alone?
Why do you
look like you haven't lost anything?
I'm making it easier for you to leave me.
That's not it.
You're too used to being left alone.
[ There is no one in this world ]
[ who is used to being left alone. ]
Next.
[ - No one. ]
- Next.
Next.
Show me your ticket and ID.
I can't go to a museum at this hour alone.
Perch?
I can't eat that now.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Maybe I should have bought
the chocolate earlier.
Speak of the devil.
How much is...
Sorry? How much is what?
I thought you left.
Why...
Would you like to have
dinner with me?
[ Dinner Mate ]